welcome everybody I'm bigger yeah yeah
here you guys are too okay so um these
are the questions that I was curious
about um and I think they'll be the
questions you guys are curious about too
I'm gonna ask a lot about the very early
days of Facebook home we were just
talking about them in the back it was
fascinating wish you could have heard it
oh oh we'll do our best to try and
reproduce it um so here's a question
that might be a little bit difficult um
how long before 2004 could something
like Facebook have succeeded like what
was the last thing that was needed to
fall into place could someone have done
it in 1995 or 2000 yeah no it's an
interesting question um there were
certain elements that we certainly
bootstrapped off of and kind of used to
hack early identity right so one of the
things that that people don't think
about that often today is early on we
wanted to establish this culture of real
identity on the service and you know
there weren't really any other online
services or communities where people
were openly their their real self before
that and one of the ways that we kind of
determined that someone was really who
they said they were and their
credentials were real where everyone had
school email addresses and I don't know
how much before 2004 assume you know
probably around 2000 all schools started
issuing email addresses but that was
really this critical thing that made it
so that we could get servers this
counterintuitive thing that um not many
other services were using so school
email addresses were the original source
of identity well that's how he knew what
school you were in right and then you
weren't just a sock puppet because you
can't just get the school to keep yeah
exactly yeah meal address yeah yeah yeah
so it also admits that people couldn't
sign up for fake accounts right right
people typically only have one school
account so having being able to
bootstrap off of that was this really
nice early thing that that helped us
establish this culture of real identity
and once we got to a few million people
or 10 million people where that culture
was established it was able to bootstrap
into something that was much bigger that
kept most of that culture even though
now obviously most people in the world
don't have emails that are issued by
some institution that vouch this or
their identity now people log in through
Facebook
now you are the source of high density
well you know it comes around yeah but
you know but but to your question about
when would it have been possible you
know one of the big trends that we see
is that the amount that any individual
shares in a given year seems to be
growing of this exponentially increasing
rate right Berg's law yeah I don't call
it that but but other people do you
heard in your first but um you know I I
mean it is this kind of social
networking version of Moore's law and
it's interesting and you know what that
suggests to me is you know if we expect
that this rate is going to double every
year then you know look out 10 years to
to the 10th is 1024 right so 10 years
from now people will be sharing about a
thousand times as many things
you know better adhesion next year
I feel like everything will be cool
anyway I just have a good I have a good
feeling about today I don't think that's
a bad omen no that's wonderful
um Sonia so I think the question is not
would Facebook have not been possible
before 2004 it would have been in some
capacity but people would have shared
less and if you fast forward five years
there's going to be a version of there
gonna be all these social services that
people are using to share way more and I
think that anyone here could be can kind
of think about you know K ten years from
now people are gonna be sharing a
thousand times as much stuff a day if
this if this trend continues what's what
things are gonna have to exist in the
world what kind of services are gonna
have to exist in order for that to be
possible Instagram for toilets um that's
the final frontier
I mean Instagram is killing it I mean
they're they're doing really well so
that's a good frontier all right when
you first launched in the very beginning
the features were sort of profile with
like a profile photo and your name and
who you are and also you included things
like what house you lived in what dorm
you lived in um and what courses you
were taking do you think it would have
worked without that would it have been
enough just to have profiles you know
it's a really interesting question and
we certainly since then have evolved and
wanted to make a more general service so
we've dropped some of those things but I
remember um there's this early debate
that Dustin and I had where we had to do
some manual work for every school that
we we're earliest Facebook ad and in
order to do that we basically went
through and we parsed the course
catalogs of the schools to make sure the
data was clean and um and I remember
having this debate where Dustin was like
we could just expend so much faster or
it would just be easier I mean we were
bound by server capacity but it would be
easier to launch new schools if we
didn't have to have course catalogs for
each school and we just had this really
long debate about what quality meant for
us and the community that we wanted to
establish and in the culture of it and
you know in retrospect you know maybe
you wouldn't have had a huge difference
on how things played out but it
definitely kind of set this tone where
there's a lot of kind of clean data on
Facebook you can rely on it it feels
like a college specific thing yeah
which was valuable early on for setting
the culture even though obviously since
then we've grown beyond that and you
know I think you guys in the projects
that you work on you're gonna have a lot
of similar questions right I mean
there's the the famous 80/20 rule where
you know you get 80% of the benefit by
doing 20% of the work but you can't just
80/20 everything right I mean there have
to be certain things that you just are
the best at right and that you go way
further than anyone else had to
establish this kind of quality bar and
have your product be the best thing
that's out there so you know whether we
had to do that one or had to do
something we had to do I think enough of
those things or else we just wouldn't
been the best service out there do you
remember when you got rid of courses
when did you stop part including course
Kaizen probably when we expanded beyond
colleges really so you kept doing
courses yeah all through girls was like
hundreds of colleges um I think we
eventually figured out a way that just
crowd-sourced and made it a bit easier
once we had enough data that we could
extrapolate from the colleges that we
had in place but we did it for probably
way longer than was rational hmm
do you do you remember how much your
first server cost you said oh yeah $85
$85 yeah and I remember that because
that was the gating factor for us
launching new schools I I mean we had
this philosophy from the very beginning
that we didn't want to be this project
it wasn't even a company at the very
beginning but we didn't want to be
burning a lot of money right we weren't
planning on raising a lot of money we
didn't want to be one of these things
that raised a bunch of money and you
know was losing a bunch of money and
then decided that we'd somehow pull it
through at the end and um so you know so
$85 for the first server put ads on the
site and the ads at the beginning where
we just were running some kind of ad
network and you murder what the first ad
was um no I don't I don't how do I get
ads um this was Eduardo's job Verizon
was I mean he was your ad sales he yeah
he basically like he was responsible for
making sure that we had enough money to
keep things running in the beginning and
you know basically I mean so it was the
server was $85 and you know Dustin and I
basically worked on kind of efficiency
and making sure that we can fit more
schools onto each server and and Eduardo
worked on selling more ads or making a
deals that we can get
ad network so that way we can we can
make more money then whenever we had
more money we rented another $85 a month
server and we kind of went from there
and some interesting way of soo never
spent money you didn't have in the
beginning not in the beginning no and
then I mean even why was the constraint
on your growth rate how many new $85 is
you could get yeah and I mean it was
actually good because I mean you know
sometimes it's really nice to have the
time to get your product to be awesome
and deal with scaling problems and one
of the things that was interesting was
um you know at the time I don't know how
many people remember this but I mean
Friendster was the service that had
massive scaling problems yeah you know
the idea was they were they grew quickly
and it was really hard for them to scale
and you know the fact that we could kind
of go college by college and and kind of
optimize the service and make it more
efficient and offer new features but
make sure that they worked I think was
really key I mean we're you're talking
about people who never built a company
before we never built any large-scale
software or anything so having the
period where we could just bake it and
you know people these days like to talk
about how these services grow super
quickly then Facebook did grow quickly
but I think it took a year for us to get
a million users and we thought that that
was incredibly fast but and and I think
it is but it wasn't as quick as a lot of
things grow today and I think actually
having that time to bake it was really
valuable for and there were like two
thousand users at Harvard that's 500x in
a year that's pretty fast
well they're I think around 4,000 or
5,000 undergrads at Harvard I remember
reading you got half of them I mean
presumably well no there was two-thirds
or three-quarters or something in the
first two weeks so I mean the thing that
we found was that basically we opened it
up at a school and and within you know a
couple of weeks then the vast majority
of students would it would be on the
surface
was there a school ever that you opened
it and it didn't work it didn't stick um
some schools took longer than others
depending on the size of the school so
what we basically did was so I launched
it at Harvard first because I wanted it
right haven't I built it for myself
I like I really want to be able to use
the service and you know this is one of
the ironies is I started building
Facebook because I wanted to use it in
college and then I immediately left
college so I didn't really get to do
that but um just expand it to everybody
else outside no yeah so it worked out
but
you know so then after Harvard all these
schools started well a lot of students
from other schools started writing to us
and asking for us to expand and we
weren't looking to start a company right
and I figured that eventually something
like this would would exist at large
scale but you know one of the one of the
interesting juxtapositions that was
going on at the time was I remember
distinctly I had this one friend who I
went and got pizza with almost every
night we did all our computer science
problem sets together at Harvard and at
the time I remember talking to him about
how I was working on this Facebook thing
and I thought it would be cool for
Harvard and I really was excited about
it because I wanted to use it but at the
same time how I thought that over time
someone would definitely go build this
version of this for the world but it
wasn't gonna be us it was going to be
you know Microsoft or you know someone
who built the software for hundreds of
millions of people it's like who were we
word college student sorry we're not
qualified in any way to build this and I
think a lot of my take away from that
was that we just kind of cared more than
those other companies about making it
exist so anyhow but back to your it back
to your kind of question and off that
tangent the first set of schools that we
launched out after Harvard were schools
that had other kind of school specific
social network so I think it was
Stanford had something Columbia had
something and I think Yale had something
so why would you choose ones that had
school specific social network because I
wanted to editors well I wanted to go to
the schools I thought would be the
hardest for us to succeed at because I
knew that if we had a product that was
better than everything else that other
students were making at other colleges
then it would be worth investing in and
putting putting time into but I didn't
want to just kind of like get into a
project where they would end up being
this huge legacy of maintaining it if
ultimately they were just going to be
different things that were as good as it
so and we thought that this was going to
be good and you know we launched it at
it was Yale Stanford Columbia and and
yeah I mean pretty quickly I think it
just so you felt probably that you could
have just gone to some random school and
it would have succeeded you chose those
because they had nascent competitors
yeah I mean I think what we saw at those
schools was people wanted to use
something like this right so we just
wanted to make sure that what we had was
like way better than anything else that
was out there worth you know putting
time into do you think I know I read in
the crimson article about when you first
launched hundreds of people sign up for
new hundreds hundreds sign up for new
Facebook website that is not the onion
that is the crimson all sometimes hard
to distinguish um Harvard students huh
um okay so uh do you think though they
said in this article that Harvard the
Harvard Computer Services people were
working on at university wide Facebook
their problem was to like they couldn't
figure out how to restrict information
enough right um do you think if that had
already existed if you had been a couple
years younger and he would come to
Harvard and this already existed do you
think you would have ever started
Facebook I don't know I mean there's
this trend that I was talking about
before where each year people share more
and more right so I think that you can
kind of math out at any given point and
I think you can look at the the internet
and say okay there's enough sharing to
support certain products right so
Wikipedia came really before Facebook
because there was a smaller amount of
sharing could support information about
all the public entities and railed right
but in order to have enough sharing to
support some basic information so you
can look up anyone and find some
interesting stuff about them then that
that required more sharing so we had to
be further along this curve and you know
made a couple years earlier someone
might have been able to do something
that was more basic but a couple years
later even a couple years from now
someone will be able to build something
that is just so much more encompassing
and allows people to learn so much more
about the people around them than what
is even built today so our kind of
continual mission and job is to keep on
building that next thing and I mean
that's what we live for at Facebook and
what excites us so even if Harvard even
if the university had built something
there would always you could have built
the next thing
yeah and it's obviously always hard to
tell exactly how things would have
played out but I mean one of the
interesting things about Facebook was it
wasn't just a picture and some basic
info and it pretty quickly gave people
the ability to share more stuff right
now and one of the early stories that I
think is pretty instructor for anyone
who's trying to build a startup is you
know we really listen to what our users
wanted right in listening means both
kind of qualitatively listening to the
words that they say
and quantitatively looking at the
behaviors that they take and you know at
the beginning we we had one profile
picture that you could have on your on
your profile that on what we observed
was there was this behavior where a lot
of people would everyday upload a new
profile picture and you know our
takeaway from this was that you know
people there was this very strong demand
to have a service where people could
share more photos and it actually wasn't
until we had the server capacity and the
engineering team bandwidth to actually
build a full photo sharing service but
that that's become obviously one of the
key parts of Facebook I think we're over
three or four hundred million photos
shared a day now someone it's pretty
crazy but you know obviously no Facebook
that that any university would have
built would have supported that right
and you know even just like that right
or it's kind of really nice right yeah
any incremental I mean they would have
just had whatever mug shot you have on
your your card right would have been
your picture so they would have chosen
the picture yeah you can keep which is
in the picture yeah I can totally see
how it would have been um do you
remember when you first showed up in
college what you plan to do afterwards
do you think you were gonna go to
graduate school or did you think you
were going to get a job when I first
went to college I actually was planning
on being a classics major I loved
classics and and and high school Latin
and Greek I just found it fascinating
and my sister actually did go on and do
that just now PhD student in classics
and we talked about this all the time it
just still fascinating to me when I was
in college I actually wasn't a computer
science major I was a psychology major I
didn't really get around to taking that
many classes because I left pretty
quickly and I actually ended up taking
more computer science classes than than
psychology classes but I was never you
know I don't know so you had no plan no
I mean you're gonna be a barista no I
probably would have um I probably would
have gotten an engineering job is my
sense and I you'd have gotten sucked in
deprogramming uh well I mean I like
programming and I really you know
growing up I always had a lot of respect
for for Microsoft and what they built
and a lot of people from Harvard go to
Microsoft and went to Microsoft and I
maybe I would have done that I don't
know it's it's really obviously hard to
say later I made this bet with my sister
Donna the
six PhD I was talking about before who
um I bet her when I was starting college
before she was that or she bet me that
she would finish college before me and
and I was like all right that's I'll
take that bad it's a good story
I don't know and um and then after after
when I dropped out I was talking to my
mom and she's like ya know I always knew
you would drop out of college I was
gonna thanks mom so they need I don't
know you know notice that you would zoom
out of the top or fall out of the bottom
I never asked me that do you think
your parents knew that you would always
like run your own show cuz you asked
them I think they'd probably say yes but
yeah I did you want to start startups no
and I mean I think that's actually a
really interesting part of this for me
is and I mean being in a place like this
we're obviously a lot of you guys are
thinking about starting these starting
companies and you know for me so much of
the lesson that that I I feel like I've
learned is I feel like it's really hard
to decide to start a company right you
know Facebook I didn't start it to start
a company I started it because I really
wanted this thing personally and I
believe that it should exist globally
although I wasn't quite sure that that
we would be able to play a role in doing
that and um it was mostly just through
kind of like wanting to build it and
having it be this hobby and getting
people around me excited that it
eventually kind of evolved into and got
the momentum to become a company but I
never really understood the psychology
of deciding that you want to start a
company before you understand what you
want to do and then I know that that's
not that that's different from your
philosophy on them no no believe me I
wish we would get more people who-who
where the company started them rather
than vice-versa none of the issues is
just it once you this gets back to the
question of why did we why did we first
open it at colleges that had competitors
I have this big fear I think of getting
locked into doing things that aren't
actually the most impactful things I'm
to me this is like the trait that
entrepreneurs have is they just have
this like laser-like ability to go find
where they can have the most impact and
you know when you take on a new project
especially if you hire people or start a
company you're doing that project and I
mean there are ways they're obviously
different ways that it can exit and all
that but I think having the
flexibility to explore a lot of
different things which you can do when
you're in college which is one of the
amazing things about being in college is
you can work on all these hobbies and
and encode a lot of stuff and try a lot
of different things it's this amazing
flexibility that I think most people
take for granted and once you decide
okay I'm going to start a company and
I'm gonna do it with someone else you
immediately now need to convince someone
else if you want to change your mind on
something and I think people really
undervalued the option value in
flexibility so as I stay in college um I
think explore what you want to do before
committing is really like the key thing
and keep yourself flexible and know I
think that that's yeah I agree
yeah but but I think in it you can
definitely do that within the framework
of a company but I think you have to be
wary about starting a company too
rigidly because you're gonna change what
you do I mean people talk about pivots
all the time as if it's like it didn't
didn't your thing didn't work so you
pivoted Facebook pivoted many times I
mean just that you know we kind of work
college and then we were not college and
then we were just a website and then we
were a platform right and um you're
gonna change what you do right and oh
you're a minister you have there's
another word for the kind of pivots
you're talking about expansions well it
that's not what people usually mean by
pivoting well you know high flexibility
yeah um I'm curious when you first
started like there's a difference
between making something where people
sign up and making something where
people keep coming back yeah right what
was it you were talking about the way
you measured people's behavior what was
the feature that kept people coming back
to Facebook over and over again once
they created their profile I mean I
think it really just gets down to what
makes humans human right I mean like
this comes back to the my studying
psychology and all that but I mean the
human brain is is kind of uniquely wired
to process things about people right
it's like when I see when I look out I
see faces I don't see you know chairs or
the room around people it's like we're
hardwired to think about people I mean
there are whole parts of you know the
visual cortex that just process the
slightest kind of micro movements of
your face to process emotion and this is
like what people are and what fascinates
them and it's how we
how we process the world actually I
heard the study in recently that I think
is interesting which is that most humans
if you if you take an MRI when they're
dreaming they dream about social
interactions and humans are the only
animal that does that so now okay but
there was no service online that I mean
it when I when I thought about the
internet before Facebook there were all
these things I thought Google and search
engines were amazing right you can type
in something and get access to any
information that you wanted but you
couldn't learn about the people around
you right and because most of that
information isn't public and just out
there ready to be indexed by by some
search engine so answer had to be a
service that gave people the power to
share the things that they wanted and
control it in the way that they wanted
and and Facebook did that and I think
that it's you know one one um definition
of technology that I think is
interesting is it extends some natural
human capacity right so glasses or
contacts extend your ability to see
right Steve Jobs once famously compared
a computer to being a bicycle for your
mind right and basically extending your
ability to think and I mean the word
computer is the Latin think together
right so it's like you're you're
thinking together the social network I
think extends people's very real social
capacity I mean you hear all these um
approximations I mean there's this
famous Dunbar's number humans have the
capacity to maintain empathetic
relationships with about a hundred fifty
people communities about a hundred fifty
people I think Facebook extends that
where you see evidence of that within
Facebook by the way do you see certain
things that stop at one hundred and
fifty um naturally when people sign up
the average amount of friends that they
get is around 150 but then over time it
can expand and you can keep in touch and
stay in touch with many more people so I
think it's like so given that I actually
think one of the lessons from that is I
do something that's fundamental right I
mean I think a lot of people in a lot of
the companies that I see are operating
on on small problems right and um it's
cool if you want to be an entrepreneur
and salva and what you're primarily
trying to do is build a company and then
solve some tangible problem but but I
think that the most interesting things
operate on these phenomena in the world
which are really just fundamental to how
humans or the world operate so what you
did was something that was fundamental
for a small market and then you just
expand them are
from beyond Harvard students to everyone
but Harvard students are sufficiently
like that well it was gross yeah it was
fundamental for me right it's like I
like I felt this need really acutely I
really wanted this right and so yeah and
then I think it's just I mean that's one
of the things that I think we were lucky
about in kind of the expansion of the
market was that it turned out that this
wasn't something that was just for
college students almost everyone in the
world has friends and family and want to
stay in touch with those people so it
ended up being a pretty ubiquitous
service in retrospect this is a bit of a
controversial question perhaps but in
retrospect do you think myspace had a
chance since once you started and you
got all the college students I mean the
college students are arguably like the
center of gravity socially right you own
all the college students it feels like
you know from the point you start
expanding out of Harvard my Space
Mountain might not have known it maybe
you didn't even know it but it seems
like in retrospect they were doomed you
know I don't I don't see it that way
actually I they could have won no it's
not about winning and losing it's about
doing something that's valuable right
and there are more than one more than
one social network not really many
I mean my view of the world is that
almost every product in category is
going to get transformed and reimagined
to be social so there were things that
myspace did that Facebook has never done
you know MySpace I think was it was a
much better service early on for meeting
new people read Facebook was never
primarily about meeting new people it
was about staying connected with with
the people that you knew and and kind of
mapping out the real relationships that
existed now I think part of the issue is
the sauce growing and they felt
threatened by that and tried to copy
what we were doing and that's like
you're never going to win that way right
it is I mean I think of all these
interesting social services and apps
that are getting built today I mean
think about all the new apps that you
guys install on your phones there are so
many interesting things and there are
eight out of the top ten iOS apps plug
into Facebook 50 percent of the top 400
apps plug into Facebook they're all kind
of socially integrated and in these ways
but companies that are getting started
now that are just trying to copy the
stuff that that the other companies are
doing just aren't aren't successful by
the way how we doing
is there anybody in charge of time 12:27
what time do we start few more minutes
all right if you will ask you a few more
questions um so you think do you think
myspace could have survived if they had
gone off into some marginal territory
like country marginally your somehow I
think that there is a real value in the
world people have a fundamental need I
think to stay connected with the people
they know and I think people have many
fundamental needs to meet new people and
expand their horizons as well and that's
never been the primary problem that
Facebook is trying to solve and and I
think it's something that we can do it's
something that someone else could do
using our platform or that someone else
could do using building it independently
and um you know I never bought the music
thing for MySpace
so I mean they they they kind of always
say that there were music service I'm
not sure why did they do that I don't
know if you have to ask them but hmm
maybe they can't they counted on bands
to spam their fans or something like
that that's a that's a powerful force in
the world so before we go I want to ask
you about how you ended up out here do
you what was always the sort of how did
how did you end up in that house in Palo
Alto was it something you decided at the
last minute I don't actually remember
you know I remember bits of the story
but you know so I first I wrote the
first version of Facebook January of
2004 right and released it in February
and um the reason why I did in January
was was because at the time Harvard had
this intersession thing it's kind of
weird and I think that they don't have a
link period anymore
I think they've changed it so now
there's no now I started yeah well you
know now I'm bad because they try to
kick out everyone who starts anything
interesting there but um but that's huh
huh that's um but um I think that I
think that they're actually trying to
change that but um but it is striking
the so now they've made it I think so
finals or before you go away for
holidays but they have this thing before
where in January you basically just have
this dead month where you could study
for finals oh my gosh where you could
study for finals
ethically coming - you could study for
finals I wondered when I saw it was
started in January it was started in
reading period yeah and it was because
you had this time whether you weren't
too busy with stuff yeah although I
actually um I probably should have been
studying there's this other story that I
think is very funny which is um I was
taking this course Rome of Augustus and
it was it was one of the core curriculum
classes that we had in the final was the
these pieces of art that you study
throughout the class and then they give
you some on the final day they show you
some of the pieces of art and you have
to write about the historical
significance of them and you know I
hadn't really done much of the reading
in the class I mostly just spent my time
programming and building stuff that I
enjoyed and you know I could have used
reading period to to study for this but
instead I spent it reading a building
Facebook so instead what I did was I am
I hacked together this website where I
went and downloaded from from the course
website the 200 or so images that were
going to be potentially on the final and
I just built this very simple page site
where it showed one of the images and
then you could contribute what you
thought was significant about it and
then you can see what other people
then I am and then you could go next to
note pulp a random one and and then I
emailed it to the class list I was like
hey guys I built a study tool anyone
that find this interesting and and
everyone just populated this thing for
me and it was wonderful and that the
professor after that they mentioned that
the grades on the final had never been
higher before so
Sonia so yeah so you Krauts were
studying so yeah so I'm pleased so and
you know a lot of interesting social
dynamics that you can apply to almost
any category that you choose to build
for but yeah so i built i built the
first version in january some of the
time I was at Harvard supposed to be
studying I actually went and visited a
couple of friends one who was at
Stanford and one who is out at Cal Tech
and and at the time I'd never really
been out to California before and you
went in January in January and what did
you think well I was really nice I
remember you know coming in to the like
affluent SFO and was driving down 101
and I saw these buildings for all these
companies like wow this is like where
these technologies company these
technology companies come from this is
amazing and and you know and then I just
looking at the weather also is awesome
and I remember I had been at Harvard for
a freshman year and I stayed there for
the summer and then sophomore year so by
the time that sophomore summer kind of
came around my friends and I were just
like okay well let's let's go somewhere
else right and let's rent a place in
California so we just had to get a place
in in Palo Alto and the idea at the time
wasn't that we actually were not
thinking about moving to California or
dropping out the actually the actual
thought that had crossed that was in our
mind was it'll be neat to be around some
of these other great companies that are
getting built one day maybe we'll find
something that will build a company out
of but surely this isn't it and so we
went out to California and and we just I
remember this conversation where one day
Dustin pulled me aside and was like you
know we were getting to have a lot of
users and where we are having an
increasing number of servers we have no
ops guy all right so we're the ops guy
and and this was before kind of ec2
right so you didn't have to so you have
to do more to manage manage your own
servers at that point and just like you
know this is this is really hard I don't
think that we can do this and take a
full course load so let's so Harvard has
this policy where you can take as much
time as you want off from school so why
don't we just take one term off and then
just try to get it under
and build the toolings that way we can
go back for spring semester and run it
more autonomously and and it'll grow and
we'll be able to run a more autonomous
lake so we did that and and of course we
raise money from Peter teal but we told
him the plan right and and kind of
explained what he told him you might go
back to school yeah and I think he
didn't believe us but you know smart new
wet work my life is just this long
history of people thinking I was going
to drop out well before I did but um but
so then you know spring term came along
and we hadn't quite built the tooling
and automation so you know let's take
another term off and then finally at
some point we we just figured that we
were that we were out there but by then
I mean we had no millions of users so
you didn't definitely decide not to go
back to hello
until you had millions of users oh yeah
yeah Wow hey I think I could still go
back Harvard Harvard is this policy
where you can go back for as long as you
want
whatever their policy was I'm sure they
would bend the rules in your case all
right are we are we done are we over is
there anybody watching the time well we
can go I have to go to mark has a
wedding he has did I do it's actually
the guy who I am who I said before I
used to go out to pizza with him every
almost every night we were doing our CS
problem sets with he's he joined
Facebook and we're really good friends
and he's getting married right after
this so I have to go and run off to that
but thank you guys